<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2 http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2.xsd">
 <p xlink:href="Chiara_PEAR_Server_REST/p/unl_ucbcn">UNL_UCBCN</p>
 <c>pear.unl.edu</c>
 <v>0.6.0</v>
 <a>0.6.0</a>
 <mp>5.0.0</mp>
 <st>beta</st>
 <l>BSD License</l>
 <m>saltybeagle</m>
 <s>This package provides the database interactions for a UC Berkeley Calendar system.</s>
 <d>This package creates and upgrades a relational database used to store event publishing details
                    formatted using the University of California Berkeley Calendar Network schema. The backend provides
                    basic functions for an event management frontend, as well as a public frontend.</d>
 <da>2008-08-21 09:39:09</da>
 <n>NOTE: This release contains database changes!
Please backup your database before installing this upgrade.

Feature Release:
* Add field to calendar table - recommendationswithinaccount. Used to store
  whether this calendar will accept recommendations from other calendars under
  the same account. This calendar users under the same account to recommend
  events to one another without requiring specific permissions over each calendar.
  Defaults to NO.
* Post install script now asks if the user would like sample event types added.
* Add console script to make grouping calendars under accounts easy.
    Ex: php calGrouper.php &quot;New or Existing Account Name&quot; calshortname1 calshortname2
* Add console script for adding accounts.
    Ex: php addAccount.php &quot;College of Engineering&quot;

Fixes:
* Update BSD license link to the UNL copy.
* Update copyright date to 2008.
* Change homepage URLs to Google Code project page.
* Minor Coding Standards fixes.</n>
 <f>37104</f>
 <g>http://pear.unl.edu/get/UNL_UCBCN-0.6.0</g>
 <x xlink:href="package.0.6.0.xml"/>
</r>
